<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BuildingDetector</string>
    <string name="hub_info">The Hub is the heart of the University. This is home to McColls, Starbucks and subway as well as the \'Grab \'n\' Go\' area, for those quick sandwich or salad purchases. \n \n Upstairs in the Hub you\'ll find work and social spaces with welcoming sofas and comfortable chairs, giving you a view over central campus. The Students\' Union head office and the Student Advice Centre are also based on the Hub Mezzanine, meaning there\'s always a buzz about the place with students and staff alike. \n \nThe Hub also doubles up as a marketplace, with local retailers and grocers pitching up on Wednesdays and Thursdays selling all sorts of homemade goods from crepes to cakes and candles to sandals. \n \nThe Hub is a place to escape, to socialise and to shop, and we\'ve brought everything together here, for you.</string>
    <string name="tech_info">TechHub is a department of computer science building.\n <b>Ground floor floor features:</b> \n Lecture theater \n CAVE \n Boardroom Th014 \n Computer science admin room THG02 \n Head of department THG11 \n Computer science Labs THG01-07 \n Computer science offices THG01-07 \n WC \n\n <b>First floor features:</b> \n Computer science labs THF01-THF07 \n Meeting room THF08 \n Research space THF09 \n Research projects lab THF01 \n Computer science staff offices THF11-THF17 \n wc \n\n Second floor features:\n Biotechnology labs THS01-THS17 \n Productivity and Innovation centre THS18-THS19\n Knowledge exchange and enterprise office THS20 \n FAS enterprise and Employability office THS21 \n Meeting room THS22\n Associate dean enterprise and employability THS23 \n TH kitchen \n wc</string>
    <string name="geo_info">At the foot of a lake, the GeoSciences building is your base on campus. As well as easy access to your tutors, facilities include our specialist laboratories, covering physical geography, geology and Geographical Information Systems (GIS). \n \n
And we now have a new purpose-built physical geography teaching laboratory, two new industry-standard analytical and research laboratories, and a geo-technical engineering laboratory.</string>
    <string name="bio_info">This a department of science building for bioscience. \n First floor features \n Florey, Linnaeus, Haeckel, Nancye Kent Perry laboratories \n Ray, Havey, Mclintock, Ross, Muller, Hooke Research Laboratory. \n Edge Hill JEOL Imaging Centre. \n Second floor features \n Offices F101-F105 \n Jenner, Vavilov, Jeans Laboratories. \n Laplace, Tansley, Morgan, Hutchinson, Latreille Research Laboratories. \n Third Floor features \n Offices S201-S206 \n

Wallace, Arrhenius, Darwin Laboratories. \n Franklin, Hodgkin Laboratories. \n WC on all floors.</string>
    <string name="cat_info">Catalyst info goes here....</string>
    <string name="law_info">1st in the UK for learning resources (National Student Survey 2021 - Law) \n \n
This building is the main learning base for our law, criminology, policing and psychology students. The three-story buildings ground floor features multiple seminar and tutorial rooms as well as a 250-seat lecture hall. The first floor is home to the school of law, criminology and policing seminar rooms and experimental facilities. \n \n
The third floor consists of psychology labs. Our Psychology labs include a group testing lab, two bi-directional observation rooms, and even a \'bar simulation lab\' for alcohol research.</string>
    <string name="bus_info">Business info goes here....</string>


</resources>